# Jonathan G. STODDART

in https://rb.gy/iwhfgm

**?** jonathangraye

Ç

OBJECTIVE: A Network Engineer with 6 years of work experience and a proven record of supporting critical infrastructure, automating tasks and working with key stakeholders to deliver projects successfully. Seeking opportunities to solve challenging problems.

## EDUCATION

Digital Technology Solutions(networking pathway) — Bachelor of Science

SEP 2022 - JUNE 2024

University of Roehampton

Grade: Expected 1st class (with Honours)

Roehampton, London

Network Engineer — Level 4 QA

SEP 2020 - JUNE 2022

Creative Music Technology — Bath Spa University 2015 - 2017 Grade: HND

Bath, Somerset

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Amazon — IT Engineer

SEP 2020 - PRESENT

Acting as an escalation point for technicians and Amazon operations teams for any IT incidents. Achievements include:

- Leading 2 pilot site launches as on-site build lead. co-ordinated internal and external stakeholders across multiple teams internationally to implement revised operational processes and new network infrastructure. Tested and deployed multiple new hardware devices for end-users in externalised network. Achieved the launch of a new warehouse management system in the UK
- Developed and implemented automated keypad provisioning of pack and Pick-to-Rebin station devices using Bash scripting. resulting in a decrease of provisioning time by 90 percent per site
- Delivered local projects and co-ordinated build efforts over 15 robotics, sortation, fulfilment, delivery and vendor flex sites
- Reduced energy footprint across local sites by participating in access switch consolidation, saving thousands of pounds a year and reducing the environmental impact of IT equipment
- Designed and developed a secure file sharing service for the Amazon Apprenticeship team to work with external provders to analyse survey data using AWS tools (IAM, S3, Transfer Family, Lambda, Organisations and Secrets Manager)
- Developed bash scripts to identify physical locations of devices from IP addresses to resolve incidents and location troubleshooting faster on large sites
- Worked with engineers and technicans to maintain a 95 percent SLA within the busiest site in the UK by ticket volumes and parcels
- Co-ordinated with senior leadership, Learning, Safety and Mechanical Engineering teams to deliver local projects which delivered on innovations within the business. Ensured that once projects were delivered, these were documented and SOPs were written in internal wikis

#### Xperience Group — IT Analyst

Jun 2018 - Sep 2020

Provided users with technical support and guidance, ensured that internal documentation was kept up to date , configured and tested new systems for customers. Key responsibilities included:

- Providing support for 100+ companies across the UK, Australia and Ireland as a team of 4, ensuring first response SLAs were met
- Migrating organisations to Azure and Microsoft 365 from on-premise systems to Azure, ensuring group policy and organisational security is maintained
- Set-up backups of SQL databases, Windows Server and user data using VEEAM abd Windows Backup in conjunction with NAS
  devices
- Wrote and maintained PowerShell scripts to manage onboarding and offboarding of users into relevant email-groups and active directory objects. Enabled end-users to have access to all relevant IT resources needed when starting based on their job-role

#### SKILLS

System Administration, Linux, Bash, Powershell, Routing Protocols (BGP, LISP, CDP, OSPF) Network administration, Firewalls, Networking Fundamentals, VPN, TCP/IP, docker, AWS (IAM, VPC, S3, EC2, Lambda, Transfer Family, DynamoDB etc)

# CERTIFICATION

- AWS Solutions Architect Associate
- AWS SysOps Administrator Associate
- COMPTIA Network+
- Microsoft Endpoint Administrator MD102

# Hobbies and Interests

- Writing, recording and playing music. Produced and played guitar for multiple award winning bands that have played festivals and venues across the country with airtime on TV and Radio
- Exploring the world, last adventure was an excursion to Taiwan to immerse myself in the culture and the amazing food!
- Hitting the pavements for stress relief or going out on my bike to train for the London to Brighton cycle ride